who is responsible here for Natura?
Amanda,
it's lunchtime,
maintenance
where it is
little paper finish really.
and as much paper as we could get was taken,
only it stays like this,
I don't even know how to move the printer.
ox,
it must be something else.
I fall,
hi there Amanda
that they sent us,
I came here to make the concept,
they just said that,
the concept doesn't work for me
that I came here to fix your day.
I fall from the workshop
of the Passenger,
this little chocolate ball here,
she has 20g of happiness.
I just wanted to know how much happiness
you need it on your day.
today, okay,
today i need a lot,
lots and 6 Passengers.
worth people of heart,
it was worth,
it was worth too much,
thank you saw?
all good,
welcome there.
bye bye,
thank you,
goodbye Aline,
thank you!